A Guide to the Barksdale Theatre Records 1945-2006 (bulk 1954-2004)
Library of Virginia
- Series XII. Photographs, 1954-1999., Extent: 10.15 cu. ft. (29 boxes). (Box 69-97)
  - Subseries 2: Plays 1954-1999.
    - My Three Angels 1967 March (Box-folder 74:2)
    - The Night of the Iguana 1967 April (Box-folder 74:3)
    - Luv 1967 September (Box-folder 74:4)
    - The owl and the pussycat 1967 November (Box-folder 74:5)
    - Generation 1968 January (Box-folder 74:6)
    - One Hundred and Some 1968 March (Box-folder 74:7)
    - Rattle of a Simple Man 1968 May (Box-folder 74:8)
    - Oliver 1968 July (Box-folder 74:9)
    - The Impossible Years 1968 September (Box-folder 74:10)
    - Irma La Douce 1968 December (Box-folder 74:11)
    - The Lion in the Winter 1969 February (Box-folder 74:12)
    - Philadelphia, Here I Come! 1969 April (Box-folder 74:13)
    - The Fantasticks 1969 June (Box-folder 74:14)
    - Cactus Flower 1969 July (Box-folder 74:15)
    - The Absence of a Cello 1969 October (Box-folder 74:16)
    - Annie Get Your Gun 1969 November (Box-folder 74:17)
    - The Hostage 1970 March (Box-folder 74:18)
    - Man of La Mancha 1970 June (Box-folder 74:19)
    - Money 1970 September (Box-folder 74:20)
    - I Do! I Do! 1970 October (Box-folder 74:21)
    - The boys in the band 1971 February (Box-folder 74:22)
    - Plaza Suite 1971 May (Box-folder 74:23)
    - The Sound of Music 1971 July (Box-folder 74:24)
    - Old Wives' Tale 1971 October (Box-folder 74:25)
    - You're a good man, Charlie Brown 1971 November (Box-folder 74:26)
    - Goodbye Charlie 1972 February (Box-folder 74:27)
    - Never too late 1972 April (Box-folder 74:28)
    - Butterflies are free 1972 June (Box-folder 74:29)
    - George Washington Slept Here 1972 August (Box-folder 74:30)
    - Gypsy 1972 November (Box-folder 74:31)
    - To be young, gifted, and black 1973 February (Box-folder 74:32)
    - The Odd Couple 1973 April (Box-folder 74:33)
    - Dracula 1973 June (Box-folder 74:34)
    - Three bags full 1973 August (Box-folder 74:35)
    - The Patriots 1973 October (Box-folder 74:36)
    - Barefoot in the park 1973 December (Box-folder 74:37)
    - The Front Page 1974 February (Box-folder 74:38)
    - Dames at sea 1974 April (Box-folder 74:39)
    - You can't take it with you 1974 April (Box-folder 74:40)
    - Long day's journey into night 1974 September (Box-folder 74:41)
    - A flea in her ear 1974 November (Box-folder 74:42)
    - That championship season 1975 January (Box-folder 74:43)
    - Godspell 1975 March (Box-folder 74:44)
    - Catch me if you can 1975 August (Box-folder 74:45)
    - Ah, Wilderness 1975 October (Box-folder 74:46)
    - Ladies in retirement 1976 January (Box-folder 74:47)
    - Unhealthy to be unpleasant (UTBU) 1976 March (Box-folder 74:48)
    - My fat friend 1976 May (Box-folder 74:49)
    - I never sang for my father 1976 July (Box-folder 74:50)
    - Rosencrantz & Guildenstern 1976 July (Box-folder 74:51)
    - You can't take it with you 1976 November (Box-folder 74:52)
    - Mark Twain 1977 January (Box-folder 75:1)
    - Visit to a small planet 1977 February (Box-folder 75:2)
    - Red, Hot, and Cole 1977 April (Box-folder 75:3)
    - The Royal Family 1977 November (Box-folder 75:4)
    - The River Niger 1978 January (Box-folder 75:5)
    - Equus 1978 February (Box-folder 75:6)
    - The Little Hut 1978 April (Box-folder 75:7)
    - Red, Hot, and Cole 1978 May (Box-folder 75:8)
    - Man of La Mancha 1978 July (Box-folder 75:9)
    - Diamond Studs 1978 October (Box-folder 75:10)
    - Unidentified 1978 (Box-folder 75:11)
    - One flew over the cuckoo's nest 1979 February (Box-folder 75:12)
    - The Good Doctor 1979 April (Box-folder 75:13)
    - The Man who came to dinner 1979 June (Box-folder 75:14)
    - Old Wives' Tale 1979 August (Box-folder 75:15)
    - The Importance of Being Earnest 1979 October (Box-folder 75:16)
    - A life in the theatre 1980 January (Box-folder 75:17)
    - Light up the sky 1980 February (Box-folder 75:18)
    - Murder at Howard Johnson's 1980 May (Box-folder 75:19)
    - The Mikado 1980 July (Box-folder 75:20)
    - Chapter Two 1980 October (Box-folder 75:21)
    - The 1940's Radio Hour 1980 December (Box-folder 75:22)
    - Da 1981 February (Box-folder 76:1)
    - Any number can die 1981 April (Box-folder 76:2)
    - H.M.S. Pinafore 1981 June (Box-folder 76:3)
    - Bad day at Black Rock 1981 October (Box-folder 76:4)
    - Blithe Spirit 1981 December (Box-folder 76:5)
    - Much ado about nothing 1982 February (Box-folder 76:6)
    - The Elephant Man 1982 April (Box-folder 76:7)
    - The Pirates of Penzance 1982 June (Box-folder 76:8)
    - Gertrude Stein, Gertrude Stein, Gertrude Stein 1982 October (Box-folder 76:9)
    - Sweeney Todd 1982 October (Box-folder 76:10)
    - George Washington slept here 1983 February (Box-folder 76:11)
    - A couple of white chicks sitting around talking 1983 April (Box-folder 76:12)
    - Patience 1983 September (Box-folder 76:13)
    - What the butler saw 1983 September (Box-folder 76:14)
    - The Middle Ages 1983 November (Box-folder 76:15)
    - Talking with... 1984 (Box-folder 77:1)
    - Here's a how-de-do 1984 (Box-folder 77:2)
    - Present Laughter 1984 February (Box-folder 77:3)
    - Foxfire 1984 April (Box-folder 77:4)
    - Joseph and the Amazing Technicolor Dreamcoat 1984 June (Box-folder 77:5)
    - Morning's at Seven 1986 February (Box-folder 77:6)
    - The Circle 1986 May (Box-folder 77:7)
    - Brighton Beach Memoirs 1986 July (Box-folder 77:8)
    - Taking my turn 1986 November (Box-folder 77:9)
    - Vanities 1987 February (Box-folder 77:10)
    - The Amorous Flea 1987 June (Box-folder 77:11)
    - The Butterfingers Angel, etc. 1987 October (Box-folder 77:12)
    - Nunsense 1988 January (Box-folder 77:13)
    - A Child's Christmas in Wales 1988 November (Box-folder 77:14)
    - The Nerd 1989 November (Box-folder 77:15)
    - Nunsense 1990 January (Box-folder 77:16)
    - On the verge 1990 September (Box-folder 77:17)
    - Stepping Out 1990 November (Box-folder 77:18)
    - The loves of Cass McGuire 1991 March (Box-folder 77:19)
    - The Zulu and The Zayda 1991 September (Box-folder 77:20)
    - Oh Coward 1991 November (Box-folder 77:21)
    - Tender Lies 1992 January (Box-folder 77:22)
    - American Beauty 1992 March (Box-folder 78:1)
    - The Road to Mecca 1992 May (Box-folder 78:2)
    - Lucky Stiff 1992 July (Box-folder 78:3)
    - Twelfth Night 1992 October (Box-folder 78:4)
    - Social security 1992 November (Box-folder 78:4a)
    - Our 40th Year Gala 1993 January (Box-folder 78:5)
    - Death of a salesman 1993 February (Box-folder 78:6)
    - Our Town 1994 January (Box-folder 78:7)
    - Falsettos 1994 March (Box-folder 78:8)
    - Love letters 1994 April (Box-folder 78:9)
    - A Day in Hollywood/A Night in the Ukraine 1994 June (Box-folder 78:10)
    - Weird Romance 1995 (Box-folder 78:11)
    - Born Yesterday 1995 (Box-folder 78:12)
    - Prelude to a Kiss 1995 (Box-folder 78:12a)
    - Once on this Island 1995 (Box-folder 78:12b)
    - The Glass Menagerie 1995 (Box-folder 78:12c)
    - The Search for signs of intelligent life in the universe 1996 January (Box-folder 78:13)
    - The Trip to Bountiful 1996 March (Box-folder 78:14)
    - Oil City Symphony 1996 May (Box-folder 78:15)
    - The Taffetas 1996 November (Box-folder 78:16)
    - The House of Blue Leaves 1997 January (Box-folder 78:17)
    - The Complete Works of Wllm Shkspr (Abridged) 1997 February (Box-folder 78:18)
    - Molly Sweeney 1997 May (Box-folder 78:19)
    - The Woman in Black 1997 September (Box-folder 78:20)
    - Red, Hot, and Cole 1997 November (Box-folder 78:21)
    - From the Mississippi Delta 1998 March (Box-folder 78:22)
    - The Young Man from Atlanta 1998 April (Box-folder 78:23)
    - The Rocky Horror Picture Show 1998 May (Box-folder 78:24)
    - Inherit the Wind 1998 September (Box-folder 78:25)
    - Golf with Alan Shepard 1999 August (Box-folder 78:26)
    - The Gift of the Magi Unknown (Box-folder 78:27)
    - Suddenly Last Summer Unknown (Box-folder 78:28)
    - The Turn of the Shrew 1994 August (Box 79)
    - Unidentified (Box 80)
    - Unidentified (Box 81)
    - Bell, Book, and Candle (OVERSIZE) 1956 June (Box-folder 82:1)
    - The Fourposter (OVERSIZE) 1958 September (Box-folder 82:2)
    - The Crucible (OVERSIZE) 1960 January (Box-folder 82:3)
    - Hotel Universe (OVERSIZE) 1961 (Box-folder 82:4)
    - John Brown's Body (OVERSIZE) 1961 July (Box-folder 82:5)
    - Mister Roberts (OVERSIZE) 1961 October (Box-folder 82:6)
    - The Solid Gold Cadillac (OVERSIZE) 1962 January (Box-folder 82:7)
    - J.B. (OVERSIZE) 1962 May (Box-folder 82:8)
    - Fallen Angels (OVERSIZE) 1962 June (Box-folder 82:9)
    - Once Upon a Mattress (OVERSIZE) 1962 September (Box-folder 82:10)
    - Critic's Choice (OVERSIZE) 1963 February (Box-folder 82:11)
    - Twelve Angry Men (OVERSIZE) 1963 April (Box-folder 82:12)
    - The Curious Savage (OVERSIZE) 1963 June (Box-folder 82:13)
    - Janus (OVERSIZE) 1963 August (Box-folder 82:14)
    - The Fantasticks (OVERSIZE) 1963 September (Box-folder 82:15)
    - A shot in the dark (OVERSIZE) 1963 December (Box-folder 82:16)
    - The Moon Is Blue (OVERSIZE) 1964 February (Box-folder 82:17)
    - Gideon (OVERSIZE) 1964 April (Box-folder 82:18)
    - Bell, Book, and Candle (OVERSIZE) 1964 June (Box-folder 82:19)
    - The Boyfriend (OVERSIZE) 1964 October (Box-folder 82:20)
    - The Marriage-Go-Round (OVERSIZE) 1965 September (Box-folder 82:21)
    - Never Too Late (OVERSIZE) 1965 October (Box-folder 82:22)
    - Mary, Mary (OVERSIZE) 1965 November (Box-folder 82:23)
    - Never Too Late (OVERSIZE) 1966 January (Box-folder 82:23a)
    - Little Mary Sunshine (OVERSIZE) 1966 April (Box-folder 82:24)
    - Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf? (OVERSIZE) 1966 May (Box-folder 82:25)
    - Boeing-Boeing (OVERSIZE) 1966 June (Box-folder 82:26)
    - The Typists (OVERSIZE) 1966 June (Box-folder 82:27)
    - The Tiger (OVERSIZE) 1966 June (Box-folder 82:28)
    - Janus (OVERSIZE) 1966 July (Box-folder 82:29)
    - Any Wednesday (OVERSIZE) 1966 September (Box-folder 82:30)
    - Stop the world, I want to get off (OVERSIZE) 1966 October (Box-folder 82:31)
    - Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf? (OVERSIZE) 1967 February (Box-folder 83:1)
    - My Three Angels (OVERSIZE) 1967 March (Box-folder 83:2)
    - The Night of the Iguana (OVERSIZE) 1967 April (Box-folder 83:3)
    - The Champagne Complex (OVERSIZE) 1967 June (Box-folder 83:4)
    - Barefoot in the Park (OVERSIZE) 1967 July (Box-folder 83:5)
    - One Hundred and Some (OVERSIZE) 1968 March (Box-folder 83:6)
    - Oliver (OVERSIZE) 1968 July (Box-folder 83:7)
    - The lion in the winter (OVERSIZE) 1969 February (Box-folder 83:8)
    - Cactus Flower (OVERSIZE) 1969 July (Box-folder 83:9)
    - Annie, Get your gun! (OVERSIZE) 1969 November (Box-folder 83:10)
    - The Hostage (OVERSIZE) 1970 March (Box-folder 83:11)
    - Man of La Mancha (OVERSIZE) 1970 June (Box-folder 83:12)
    - I do! I do! (OVERSIZE) 1970 October (Box-folder 83:13)
    - The boys in the band (OVERSIZE) 1971 February (Box-folder 83:14)
    - Three men on a horse (OVERSIZE) 1971 April (Box-folder 83:15)
    - Plaza Suite (OVERSIZE) 1971 May (Box-folder 83:16)
    - The Sound of Music (OVERSIZE) 1971 July (Box-folder 83:17)
    - You're A Good Man, Charlie Brown (OVERSIZE) 1971 November (Box-folder 83:17a)
    - Butterflies are free (OVERSIZE) 1972 June (Box-folder 83:18)
    - George Washington Slept Here (OVERSIZE) 1972 August (Box-folder 83:19)
    - Gypsy (OVERSIZE) 1972 November (Box-folder 83:20)
    - To be Young, Gifted, and Black (OVERSIZE) 1973 February (Box-folder 84:1)
    - The Odd Couple (OVERSIZE) 1973 April (Box-folder 84:2)
    - Dracula (OVERSIZE) 1973 June (Box-folder 84:3)
    - Three bags full (OVERSIZE) 1973 August (Box-folder 84:4)
    - The Patriots (OVERSIZE) 1973 October (Box-folder 84:5)
    - The Front Page (OVERSIZE) 1974 February (Folder 84:6)
    - You can't take it with you (OVERSIZE) 1974 August (Box-folder 84:7)
    - Long day's journey into night (OVERSIZE) 1974 September (Box-folder 84:8)
    - A Flea in her Ear (OVERSIZE) 1974 November (Box-folder 84:9)
    - That championship season (OVERSIZE) 1975 January (Box-folder 84:10)
    - Catch me if you can (OVERSIZE) 1975 August (Box-folder 84:11)
    - Ah, Wilderness (OVERSIZE) 1975 October (Box-folder 84:12)
    - Ladies in retirement (OVERSIZE) 1976 January (Box-folder 84:13)
    - Unhealthy to be unpleasant (OVERSIZE) 1976 March (Box-folder 84:14)
    - My fat friend (OVERSIZE) 1976 May (Box-folder 84:15)
    - Rosencrantz and Guildenstern are dead (OVERSIZE) 1976 July (Box-folder 84:16)
    - How the other half lives (OVERSIZE) 1976 September (Box-folder 84:17)
    - You can't take it with you (OVERSIZE) 1976 November (Box-folder 84:18)
    - Visit to a small planet (OVERSIZE) 1977 February (Box-folder 84:19)
    - Red, Hot, and Cole (OVERSIZE) 1977 April (Box-folder 84:20)
    - The Royal family (OVERSIZE) 1977 November (Box-folder 84:21)
    - Equus (OVERSIZE) 1978 February (Box-folder 84:22)
    - The Little Hut (OVERSIZE) 1978 April (Box-folder 84:23)
    - Red, Hot, and Cole (OVERSIZE) 1978 May (Box-folder 84:24)
    - Man of La Mancha (OVERSIZE) 1978 July (Box-folder 84:25)
    - Diamond Studs (OVERSIZE) 1978 October (Box-folder 84:26)
    - One flew over the cuckoos nest (OVERSIZE) 1979 February (Box-folder 84:27)
    - The Good Doctor (OVERSIZE) 1979 April (Box-folder 84:28)
    - The Man who came to dinner (OVERSIZE) 1979 June (Box-folder 84:29)
    - Old Wives' Tale (OVERSIZE) 1979 August (Box-folder 84:30)
    - The Importance of Being Earnest (OVERSIZE) 1979 October (Box-folder 84:31)
    - Light up the sky (OVERSIZE) 1980 February (Box-folder 85:1)
    - Murder at the Howard Johnson's (OVERSIZE) 1980 May (Box-folder 85:2)
    - Chapter Two (OVERSIZE) 1980 October (Box-folder 85:3)
    - The 1940's Radio Hour (OVERSIZE) 1980 December (Box-folder 85:4)
    - Da (OVERSIZE) 1981 February (Box-folder 85:5)
    - Any number can die (OVERSIZE) 1981 April (Box-folder 85:6)
    - H.M.S. Pinafore (OVERSIZE) 1981 June (Box-folder 85:7)
    - Bad day at Black Rock (OVERSIZE) 1981 October (Box-folder 85:8)
    - Blithe Spirit (OVERSIZE) 1981 December (Box-folder 85:9)
    - Much ado about nothing (OVERSIZE) 1982 February (Box-folder 85:10)
    - The Elephant Man (OVERSIZE) 1982 April (Box-folder 85:11)
    - The Pirates of Penzance (OVERSIZE) 1982 June (Box-folder 85:12)
    - Sweeney Todd (OVERSIZE) 1982 October (Box-folder 85:13)
    - A couple of white chicks sitting around talking (OVERSIZE) 1983 April (Box-folder 85:14)
    - Patience (OVERSIZE) 1983 September (Box-folder 85:15)
    - What the butler saw (OVERSIZE) 1983 September (Box-folder 85:16)
    - Foxfire (OVERSIZE) 1984 April (Box-folder 85:17)
    - Joseph and the Amazing Technicolor Dreamcoat (OVERSIZE) 1984 June (Box-folder 85:18)
    - The Butterfingers Angel, etc. (OVERSIZE) 1987 October (Box-folder 85:19)
    - On the verge (OVERSIZE) 1990 September (Box-folder 85:20)
    - The Cave Dwellers (OVERSIZE) Unknown (Box-folder 85:21)
    - Unidentified (OVERSIZE) (Box 86)
    - Twelve Angry Men (OVERSIZE) 1962 (Box 87)
    - A Shot in the Dark (OVERSIZE) 1963 (Box 87)
    - The Fantasticks (OVERSIZE) 1963 (Box 87)
    - The Moon is Blue (OVERSIZE) 1964 (Box 87)
    - A Shot in the Dark (OVERSIZE) 1965 (Box 87)
    - Sunday in New York (OVERSIZE) 1965 (Box 87)
    - Take Her She's Mine (OVERSIZE) 1965 (Box 87)
    - The Owl and the Pussycat (OVERSIZE) 1967 (Box 88)
    - Generation (OVERSIZE) 1968 (Box 88)
    - Irma La Douce (OVERSIZE) 1968 (Box 88)
    - Oliver (OVERSIZE) 1968 (Box 88)
    - One Hundred and Some (OVERSIZE) 1968 (Box 88)
    - Rattle of a Simple Man (OVERSIZE) 1968 (Box 88)
    - Annie Get Your Gun (OVERSIZE) 1969 (Box 89)
    - Cactus Flower (OVERSIZE) 1969 (Box 89)
    - The Absence of a Cello (OVERSIZE) 1969 (Box 89)
    - The Boys in the Band (OVERSIZE) 1969 (Box 89)
    - The Fantasticks (OVERSIZE) 1969 (Box 89)
    - Money (OVERSIZE) 1970 (Box 90)
    - The Hostage (OVERSIZE) 1970 (Box 90)
    - Tons of Money (OVERSIZE) 1970 (Box 90)
    - Old Wives' Tale (OVERSIZE) 1971 (Box 90)
    - Goodbye Charlie (OVERSIZE) 1972 (Box 91)
    - Never too late (OVERSIZE) 1972 (Box 91)
    - Barefoot in the Park (OVERSIZE) 1973 (Box 91)
    - The Patriots (OVERSIZE) 1973 (Box 91)
    - Dames at Sea (OVERSIZE) 1974 (Box 91)
    - The Front Page (OVERSIZE) 1974 (Box 91)
    - That Championship Season (OVERSIZE) 1975 (Box 91)
    - The Elephant Man (OVERSIZE) 1982 (Box 91)
    - Unknown (OVERSIZE) (Box 92)
  - Subseries 3: Buildings 1957-1996 (Box 93)
    Includes photographs of Hanover Tavern interior and exterior; Amphitheatre at Hanover Tavern; Strawberry Banks; and Willow Lawn. Also includes copies of turn of the century photographs of Richmond.
  - Subseries 4: Contact sheets 1996-1999
    This subseries is housed in 1 box and includes contacts sheets.
    - Das Barbecu 1996 July (Box-folder 94:1)
    - The House of Blue Leaves 1997 January (Box-folder 94:2)
    - The Complete Works of Wllm Shkspr (Abridged) 1997 February (Box-folder 94:3)
    - Molly Sweeney 1997 May (Box-folder 94:4)
    - Blues in the Night 1997 June (Box-folder 94:5)
    - The Woman in Black 1997 September (Box-folder 94:6)
    - The Young Man from Atlanta 1998 April (Box-folder 94:7)
    - Golf with Alan Shepard 1999 August (Box-folder 94:8)
    - Red, Hot, and Cole n.d. (Box-folder 94:9)
    - Unidentified (Box-folder 94:10)
    - Unidentified (Box-folder 94:11)
    - Unidentified (Box-folder 94:12)
  - Subseries 5: Negatives 1958-1997 (Box-folder 95:1)
    This subseries is housed in 1 box and includes negatives. Also included are negative sheets for the book, Going On... Barksdale Theatre The First Thirty-One Years, and some negatives for various family and vacation events, 1960-1973.
    - The Fourposter 1958 (Box-folder 95:1)
    - Mister Roberts 1961 (Box-folder 95:2)
    - Joseph and the Amazing Technicolor Dreamcoat 1984 (Box-folder 95:3)
    - The Complete Works of Wllm Shkspr (Abridged) 1997 (Box-folder 95:4)
    - Going On...Barksdale Theatre: The First Thirty-One Years (Box-folder 95:5)
    - Going On...Barksdale Theatre: The First Thirty-One Years (Box-folder 95:6)
    - Going On...Barksdale Theatre: The First Thirty-One Years (Box-folder 95:7)
    - Going On...Barksdale Theatre: The First Thirty-One Years (Box-folder 95:8)
    - Going On...Barksdale Theatre: The First Thirty-One Years (Box-folder 95:9)
    - Going On...Barksdale Theatre: The First Thirty-One Years (Box-folder 95:10)
    - Kevin Kilgore (Box-folder 95:11)
    - Family (Box-folder 95:12)
    - Thanksgiving 1973 (Box-folder 95:13)
    - Vacation 1960 (Box-folder 95:14)
    - Miscellaneous ca. 1960 (Box-folder 95:15)
    - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 95:16)
    - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 95:17)
  - Subseries 6: Slides 1962-1988 (Box 96)
    Includes negatives of productions, travels, Hanover Tavern, and family.
  - Subseries 7: Miscellaneous 1957-1997
    This subseries is housed in 1 box and includes various photographs of family events, holidays, the Barksdale truck, Barksdale Invitational Tennis Tournament 1967, Christmas, yard sale 1996, and photographs used in the book, Going On...Barksdale Theatre: The First Thirty-One Years.
    - Barksdale truck (Box-folder 97:1)
    - Barksdale Invitational Tennis Tournament 1967 (Box-folder 97:2)
    - Barksdale Train 1957-1958 (Box-folder 97:3)
    - Christmas n.d. (Box-folder 97:4)
    - Construction n.d. (Box-folder 97:5)
    - Events ca. 1960s (Box-folder 97:6)
    - Events ca. 1990s (Box-folder 97:7)
    - Event and yard sale 1996 (Box-folder 97:8)
    - Events 1997 (Box-folder 97:9)
    - Events 1999 (Box-folder 97:10)
    - Family 1957-1971 (Box-folder 97:11)
    - Family 1972-1980 (Box-folder 97:12)
    - Going On...Barksdale Theatre: The First Thirty-One Years (Box-folder 97:13)
      Pages 1-100
    - Going On...Barksdale Theatre: The First Thirty-One Years (Box-folder 97:14)
      Pages 101-199
    - Going On...Barksdale Theatre: The First Thirty-One Years (Box-folder 97:15)
      Pages 200-249
    - Miscellaneous n.d. (Box-folder 97:16)
    - Outdoor ca. 1950s (Box-folder 97:17)
    - Yard sale 1979 (Box-folder 97:18)
- Series XIII. Audio Visual Materials, 1981-1992., Extent: 3.5 cu. ft. (10 boxes). (Box 98-107)
  The Audio-Visual Materials Series is housed in 10 boxes and arranged into videos (Boxes 98-100), audio cassettes (Box 101), and reel to reel tapes (Boxes 102-107). In May 2005 Bill Rice and the staff at the Virginia Information Technology Agency (VITA) transferred original recordings to VHS, creating three copies of each master: service copy, preservation copy, and duplication master. The audio cassettes and reel to reel tapes have not yet been reformatted and are unavailable due to conservation and preservation concerns.
  Videos listed below.
  - Bad day at Black Rock 1981 (Box 98)
  - Blithe Spirit 1981 (Box 98)
  - Much Ado About Nothing 1982 (Box 98)
  - The Elephant Man 1982 (Box 98)
  - Pirates of Penzance 1982 (Box 98)
  - Couple of White Chicks Sitting around talking 1983 (Box 98)
  - What the Butler Saw 1983 (Box 98)
  - Patience 1983 (Box 98)
  - Foxfire 1984 (Box 98)
  - Middle Ages 1984 (Box 98)
  - Taking my Turn 1986 (Box 98)
  - Brighton Beach Memoirs 1986 (Box 98)
  - The Circle 1986 (Box 98)
  - Joseph and the Amazing Technicolor Dreamcoast (Tour) 1986 (Box 99)
  - Vanities 1987 (Box 99)
  - Joseph and the Amazing Technicolor Dreamcoat 1987 (Box 99)
  - A Child's Christmas in Wales 1988 (Box 99)
  - Painting Christmas 1988 (Box 99)
  - The Nerd 1989 (Box 99)
  - Wenceslaus Square 1989 (Box 99)
  - On the Verge 1990 (Box 99)
  - Land of Fire 1990 (Box 99)
  - The Importance of Being Earnest in Love 1990 (Box 99)
  - The Zulu and the Zada 1991 (Box 99)
  - Oh, Coward 1991 (Box 99)
  - Home Games 1991 (Box 100)
  - This Lady's Not for Burning 1991 (Box 100)
  - The Loves of Cass McGuire 1991 (Box 100)
  - Lucky Stiff 1992 (Box 100)
  - Tender Lies 1992 (Box 100)
  - American Beauty 1992 (Box 100)
  - Road to Mecca 1992 (Box 100)
  - Social Security 1992 (Box 100)
  - Death of a Salesman 1992 (Box 100)
  - Nunsense n.d. (Box 100)
  - Audio cassettes, miscellaneous (Box 101)
    (some digitized)
  - Reel to reel tapes, miscellaneous (Box 102-107)
- Series XIV. Artifacts/Ephemera, 1954-2000., Extent: 1 cu. ft. (2 boxes). (Box 108-109)
  The Artifacts Series is housed in 2 boxes. Included are framed programs from John Golden Theatre; Plaque for Helen Walsh, Barksdale Board member; Brass Pass for Marian Herget; and a Barksdale Theatre sweatshirt.